Opis programu;Description;Opis programu;Opis programu;Opis programu
Nazwa zestawienia;Composition name;Nazwa zestawienia;Nazwa zestawienia;Nazwa zestawienia
Wygenerowany plik zestawienia należy przesłać do ALNOR Sp. z o.o.;Generated ordering file ought to be sent to ALNOR Sp z o.o.;Generated ordering file ought to be sent to ALNOR Sp z o.o.;Generated ordering file ought to be sent to ALNOR Sp z o.o.;Generated ordering file ought to be sent to ALNOR Sp z o.o.
tel;phone;phone;phone;phone
izolowany;isolated;isolated;isolated;isolated
izolowana;isolated;isolated;isolated;isolated
izolowane;isolated;isolated;isolated;isolated
Zmiany będą widoczne po ponownym uruchomieniu aplikacji;Changes will be available after restart;Changes will be available after restart;Changes will be available after restart;Changes will be available after restart
Zamówienie na preferencyjnych warunkach, ze względu na przesłanie danych przygotowanych na produkcję.;This order is on preferential conditions, thanks to sending data prepared on production.;This order is on preferential conditions, thanks to sending data prepared on production.;This order is on preferential conditions, thanks to sending data prepared on production.;This order is on preferential conditions, thanks to sending data prepared on production.
Aby zachować zgodność z obliczeniami powierzchni, prowadzonymi w ALNORze należy w polu zaokrągleń "m2" zachować wartość 0.8 m2.;To keep compatibility with ALNOR calculations of surface, in "round" field "m2" keep value of 0.8 m2.;To keep compatibility with ALNOR calculations of surface, in "round" field "m2" keep value of 0.8 m2.;To keep compatibility with ALNOR calculations of surface, in "round" field "m2" keep value of 0.8 m2.;To keep compatibility with ALNOR calculations of surface, in "round" field "m2" keep value of 0.8 m2.
Po wybraniu elemenu z listy podajemy jego główne wymiary np. dla łuku podajemy tylko przekrój A i B, resztę wymiarów i parametrów wygeneruje program, można je oczywiście zmienić.;After choosing element from the list, main measurements will appear eg. for bend should be put only section A and B, rest of measurements and parameters are generated by program, if there is any need they could be changed.;After choosing element from the list, main measurements will appear eg. for bend should be put only section A and B, rest of measurements and parameters are generated by program, if there is any need they could be changed.;After choosing element from the list, main measurements will appear eg. for bend should be put only section A and B, rest of measurements and parameters are generated by program, if there is any need they could be changed.;After choosing element from the list, main measurements will appear eg. for bend should be put only section A and B, rest of measurements and parameters are generated by program, if there is any need they could be changed.
Przycisk "Odśwież" spowoduje odnowienie rysunku elementu wg. podanych wymiarów.;Button "Refresh" causes renovation of element drawing according to given measurements.;Button "Refresh" causes renovation of element drawing according to given measurements.;Button "Refresh" causes renovation of element drawing according to given measurements.;Button "Refresh" causes renovation of element drawing according to given measurements.
Zdefiniowany wymiarowo element umieszczamy w zestawieniu przyciskając "Dodaj".;After defined element and its measurements, place into composition and press "Add".;After defined element and its measurements, place into composition and press "Add".;After defined element and its measurements, place into composition and press "Add".;After defined element and its measurements, place into composition and press "Add".
Pozycje możemy też usuwać z zestawienia ("Usuń"), pobierać z zestawienia do edycji ("Edytuj"). Możemy też wstawić element w środek zestawienia przyciskiem "Wstaw za".;Unnecessary positions could be removed from composition by pressing button "Remove", composition could be edited (button "Edit"). Button "Put into by" gives opportunity to add element.;Unnecessary positions could be removed from composition by pressing button "Remove", composition could be edited (button "Edit"). Button "Put into by" gives opportunity to add element.;Unnecessary positions could be removed from composition by pressing button "Remove", composition could be edited (button "Edit"). Button "Put into by" gives opportunity to add element.;Unnecessary positions could be removed from composition by pressing button "Remove", composition could be edited (button "Edit"). Button "Put into by" gives opportunity to add element.
Do wybrania elementu z listy kształtek można też zamiast myszki użyć klawiszy PgDn PgUp.;If you want to choose element from the list, instead mouse use keys PgDn PgUp.;If you want to choose element from the list, instead mouse use keys PgDn PgUp.;If you want to choose element from the list, instead mouse use keys PgDn PgUp.;If you want to choose element from the list, instead mouse use keys PgDn PgUp.
Aby obracać widok trójwymiarowy elementu, najeżdżamy na niego myszką i trzymając wciśnięty lewy klawisz obracamy widok 3D.;To turn three-dimensional view of element, run into it by mouse and hold left key pressed and then turn 3D view.;To turn three-dimensional view of element, run into it by mouse and hold left key pressed and then turn 3D view.;To turn three-dimensional view of element, run into it by mouse and hold left key pressed and then turn 3D view.;To turn three-dimensional view of element, run into it by mouse and hold left key pressed and then turn 3D view.
Możemy też powiększać i zmniejszać widok trójwymiarowy klawiszami "+" "-". ;Three-dimensional view can be enlarge or diminish with keys "+" "-".;Three-dimensional view can be enlarge or diminish with keys "+" "-".;Three-dimensional view can be enlarge or diminish with keys "+" "-".;Three-dimensional view can be enlarge or diminish with keys "+" "-".
Wciśnięcie prawego klawisza myszki spowoduje obrót obiektu tylko wokół osi poziomej;Pressing the mouse's right button will cause the turn of object around horizontal axis only;Pressing the mouse's right button will cause the turn of object around horizontal axis only;Pressing the mouse's right button will cause the turn of object around horizontal axis only;Pressing the mouse's right button will cause the turn of object around horizontal axis only
Gotowe zestawienie, po podaniu "Danych osobowych i opisowych" należy zapisać w pliku ("Zapisz") i przesłać do ALNOR Sp. z o.o. na adres podany powyżej, jako załącznik do e-maila.;Ready composition, after filling in "Personal details and data description", should be saved in file ("Saved") and send to ALNOR Sp. z o.o. on given address above, as enclosure in e-mail.;Ready composition, after filling in "Personal details and data description", should be saved in file ("Saved") and send to ALNOR Sp. z o.o. on given address above, as enclosure in e-mail.;Ready composition, after filling in "Personal details and data description", should be saved in file ("Saved") and send to ALNOR Sp. z o.o. on given address above, as enclosure in e-mail.;Ready composition, after filling in "Personal details and data description", should be saved in file ("Saved") and send to ALNOR Sp. z o.o. on given address above, as enclosure in e-mail.
Zestawienie można również zapisać roboczo dla własnych potrzeb w pliku Excela (uwaga, ten format nie służy do przesłania do Alnora).;The composition can also be saved as  a working version for own needs in Excel (Attention, this file is not suitable to send to Alnor).;The composition can also be saved as  a working version for own needs in Excel (Attention, this file is not suitable to send to Alnor).;The composition can also be saved as  a working version for own needs in Excel (Attention, this file is not suitable to send to Alnor).;The composition can also be saved as  a working version for own needs in Excel (Attention, this file is not suitable to send to Alnor).
Polska;English;Polska;Polska;Polska
O programie;About;About;About;About
Odejścia generują różne ramki;Outlest generates different frames;Outlest generates different frames;Outlest generates different frames;Outlest generates different frames
Grubość blachy za mała;Plate thickness too small;Plate thickness too small;Plate thickness too small;Plate thickness too small
wersja; version; wersja; wersja; wersja
ALNOR Systemy wentylacji Sp. z o.o.;Alnor Ventilation Systems;ALNOR Systemy wentylacji Sp. z o.o.;ALNOR Systemy wentylacji Sp. z o.o.;ALNOR Systemy wentylacji Sp. z o.o.
ul.Zwierzyniecka 8b;  8b, Zwierzyniecka Street;  ul.Zwierzyniecka 8b;  ul.Zwierzyniecka 8b;  ul.Zwierzyniecka 8b
00-719 Warszawa;00-719 Warsaw;00-719 Warsaw;00-719 Warsaw;00-719 Warsaw
Plik;File;Plik;Plik;Plik
Promień można podać równy 0 albo większy od 99mm;Ray should be equal 0, or longer then 99;Ray should be equal 0, or longer then 99;Ray should be equal 0, or longer then 99;Ray should be equal 0, or longer then 99
Nowy;New;Nowy;Nowy;Nowy
Pobierz;Download;Pobierz;Pobierz;Pobierz
Zapisz;Save;Zapisz;Zapisz;Zapisz
Eksportuj;Export;Eksportuj;Eksportuj;Eksportuj
Ustawienia;Settings;Ustawienia;Ustawienia;Ustawienia
Przywróć domyślne ustawienia po zmianie elementu;Restore shrewd settings after changing of the element;Przywróć domyślne ustawienia po zmianie elementu;Przywróć domyślne ustawienia po zmianie elementu;Przywróć domyślne ustawienia po zmianie elementu
Pamiętaj wartości przy zmianie elementu;Remember settings after changing elements;Pamiętaj wartości przy zmianie elementu;Pamiętaj wartości przy zmianie elementu;Pamiętaj wartości przy zmianie elementu
Kolory;Colors;Kolory;Kolory;Kolory
Tło rysunku;Draw background;Tło rysunku;Tło rysunku;Tło rysunku
Kreska rysunku;Drawing line;Kreska rysunku;Kreska rysunku;Kreska rysunku
Info;Info;Info;Info;Info
Język;Language;Language;Language;Language
O programu;About programme;O programu;O programu;O programu
Biblioteka CSGL;CSGL Library;Biblioteka CSGL;Biblioteka CSGL;Biblioteka CSGL
Dane osobowe i opisowe;Personal details and data description;Dane osobowe i opisowe;Dane osobowe i opisowe;Dane osobowe i opisowe
Suma blachy;Amount of steel;Suma blachy;Suma blachy;Suma blachy
System kształtek;Ventilation elements;System kształtek;System kształtek;System kształtek
Prostokątne izolowane;Rectangular isolated;Prostokątne izolowane;Prostokątne izolowane;Prostokątne izolowane
Prostokątne;Rectangular;Prostokątne;Prostokątne;Prostokątne
Element użytkownika;User elements;Elementy użytkownika;Elementy użytkownika;Elementy użytkownika
Elementy;Elements;Elementy;Elementy;Elementy
Symbol;Symbol;Symbol;Symbol;Symbol
Oznaczenie;Mark;Oznaczenie;Oznaczenie;Oznaczenie
Odśwież;Refresh;Odśwież;Odśwież;Odśwież
Nazwa;Name;Nazwa;Nazwa;Nazwa
Symbol;Symbol;Symbol;Symbol;Symbol
Sztuk;Unit;Sztuk;Sztuk;Sztuk
Materiał;Material;Materiał;Materiał;Materiał
Przekrój;Section;Przekrój;Przekrój;Przekrój
Uwagi;Remarks;Uwagi;Uwagi;Uwagi
Odśwież;Refresh;Odśwież;Odśwież;Odśwież
Dodaj;Add;Dodaj;Dodaj;Dodaj
Usuń;Delete;Usuń;Usuń;Usuń
Wartość;Value;Value;Value;Value
poza zakresem;is out of range;is out of range;is out of range;is out of range
Edytuj;Edit;Edytuj;Edytuj;Edytuj
Wstaw za;Put into for;Wstaw za;Wstaw za;Wstaw za
Blacha;Steel;Blacha;Blacha;Blacha
Wykonanie;Realization;Wykonanie;Wykonanie;Wykonanie
Kl.szczel.;Tightness class;Kl. szczel.;Kl. szczel.;Kl. szczel.
L.wzmoc.;Nr frm brace;L.wzmoc.;L.wzmoc.;L.wzmoc.
RamkiWL;Frm in;RamkiWL;RamkiWL;RamkiWL
RamkiWYL;Frm out;RamkiWYL;RamkiWYL;RamkiWYL
RamkiOd;Frm outfall;RamkiOd;RamkiOd;RamkiOd
Anuluj;Cancel;Anuluj;Anuluj;Anuluj
Płaszcz zew.;Outer jacket;Płaszcz zew.;Płaszcz zew.;Płaszcz zew.
Grubość izolacji;Insulation thick.;Grubość izolacji;Grubość izolacji;Grubość izolacji
Dane;Data;Dane;Dane;Dane
OK;OK;OK;OK;OK
Zamawiający;Customer;Zamawiający;Zamawiający;Zamawiający
Opis programu;Desctiption;Opis programu;Opis programu;Opis programu
Uwaga;Attention;Uwaga;Uwaga;Uwaga
Uwagi;Remarks;Remarks;Remarks;Remarks
Kliknij na widok i obracaj kształtkę, +,- zbliża oddala.;Click at view and turn fitting, +,- make closer or away.;Kliknij na widok i obracaj kształtkę, +,- zbliża oddala.;Kliknij na widok i obracaj kształtkę, +,- zbliża oddala.;Kliknij na widok i obracaj kształtkę, +,- zbliża oddala.
Zbyt mała wartość;To small value;Zbyt mała wartość;Zbyt mała wartość;Zbyt mała wartość
Ocynk;Galvanised sheet;Ocynk;Ocynk;Ocynk
Kwasówka;Acid-resistant sheet;Kwasówka;Kwasówka;Kwasówka
Aluminium;Aluminium;Aluminium;Aluminium;Aluminium
Niskociśnieniowe;Low pressure;Niskociśnieniowe;Niskociśnieniowe;Niskociśnieniowe
Średniociśnieniowe;Medium pressure;Średniociśnieniowe;Średniociśnieniowe;Średniociśnieniowe
standard;standard;standard;standard;standard
krzyżowe;cross type;krzyżowe;krzyżowe;krzyżowe
Kanał prostokątny;Square duct;Kanał prostokątny;Kanał prostokątny;Kanał prostokątny
Łuk symetryczny;Symetric elbow;Łuk symetryczny;Łuk symetryczny;Łuk symetryczny
Redukcja sym.;Symmetric reducer ;Redukcja sym.;Redukcja sym.;Redukcja sym.
Redukcja kwadrat-koło sym.;Symmetric reducer circle-square;Redukcja kwadrat-koło sym.;Redukcja kwadrat-koło sym.;Redukcja kwadrat-koło sym.
Redukcja kwadrat-koło asym.;Asymmetric reducer circle-square;Redukcja kwadrat-koło asym.;Redukcja kwadrat-koło asym.;Redukcja kwadrat-koło asym.
Redukcja asym.;Asymmetric reducer;Redukcja asym.;Redukcja asym.;Redukcja asym.
Łuk redukcyjny;Diffuser reducer;Łuk redukcyjny;Łuk redukcyjny;Łuk redukcyjny
Łuk dyfuzorowany;Diffuser elbow;Łuk dyfuzorowany;Łuk dyfuzorowany;Łuk dyfuzorowany
Kolano redukcyjne;Reducer bend;Kolano redukcyjne;Kolano redukcyjne;Kolano redukcyjne
Kolano symetryczne;Symmetric bend;Kolano symetryczne;Kolano symetryczne;Kolano symetryczne
Zaślepka prostokątna;Rectangular  end cap;Zaślepka prostokątna;Zaślepka prostokątna;Zaślepka prostokątna
Trójnik z odej. prostokątnym;Tee-piece with rectangular outfall;Trójnik z odej. prostokątnym;Trójnik z odej. prostokątnym;Trójnik z odej. prostokątnym
Trójnik z odej. okrągłymi;Tee-piece with round outfall;Trójnik z odej. okrągłymi;Trójnik z odej. okrągłymi;Trójnik z odej. okrągłymi
Trójnik symetryczny;Symmetric tee-piece;Trójnik symetryczny;Trójnik symetryczny;Trójnik symetryczny
Odsadzka sym.;Symmetric offset pipe;Odsadzka sym.;Odsadzka sym.;Odsadzka sym.
Odsadzka asym.;Asymmetric offset pipe;Odsadzka asym.;Odsadzka asym.;Odsadzka asym.
Nakładka na rurę;End cap;Nakładka na rurę;Nakładka na rurę;Nakładka na rurę
Czwórnik z odej. prostokątnym;Cross-pieces with rectangular  outfall ;Czwórnik z odej. prostokątnym;Czwórnik z odej. prostokątnym;Czwórnik z odej. prostokątnym
Czwórnik z odej. okrągłymi;Cross-pieces with round outfall ;Czwórnik z odej. okrągłymi;Czwórnik z odej. okrągłymi;Czwórnik z odej. okrągłymi
Trójnik orłowy;Twin bend;Trójnik orłowy;Trójnik orłowy;Trójnik orłowy
Trójnik z od. łukowym;Tee-piece with elbow outfall;Trójnik z od. łukowym;Trójnik z od. łukowym;Trójnik z od. łukowym
Trójnik portkowy;Twin bend;Trójnik portkowy;Trójnik portkowy;Trójnik portkowy
Kanał prost. skośny;Skew rectangular duct;Kanał prost. skośny;Kanał prost. skośny;Kanał prost. skośny
Kanał prostopadły;Perpendicular duct;Kanał prostopadły;Kanał prostopadły;Kanał prostopadły
Trójnik skośny;Skew tee-piece;Trójnik skośny;Trójnik skośny;Trójnik skośny
nie może być większe od;cannot be bigger than;nie może być większe od;nie może być większe od;nie może być większe od
Wymiar d musi być większy niż b;"d" must be bigger than "b";Wymiar d musi być większy niż b;Wymiar d musi być większy niż b;Wymiar d musi być większy niż b
b musi być większe lub równe d;"b" must be bigger or equal "d";b musi być większe lub równe d;b musi być większe lub równe d;b musi być większe lub równe d
Złe dane;Incorrect data;Złe dane;Złe dane;Złe dane
musi być większe od;must be bigger than;musi być większe od;musi być większe od;musi być większe od
Za duży wymiar w; w is too big;Za duży wymiar w;Za duży wymiar w;Za duży wymiar w
Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d1;"b" must be bigger or equal "d1";Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d1;Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d1;Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d1
Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d;"b" must be bigger or equal "d";Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d;Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d;Wymiar b musi być większy lub równy d
Wymiar d musi być większy lub równy b;"d" must be bigger or equal "b";"b" must be bigger or equal "d";"b" must be bigger or equal "d";"b" must be bigger or equal "d"
Za duże d;d is too big;Za duże d;Za duże d;Za duże d
Za małe L;L is too small;Za małe L;Za małe L;Za małe L
Za duże f;f is too big;Za duże f;Za duże f;Za duże f
a musi być większe lub równe c;"a" must be bigger or equal "c";"a" must be bigger or equal "c";"a" must be bigger or equal "c";"a" must be bigger or equal "c"
g musi być mniejsze niż d;g must be less than d;g must be less than d;g must be less than d;g must be less than d
d1 musi być mniejsze niż d;d1 must be less than d;d1 must be less than d;d1 must be less than d;d1 must be less than d
Wartości e oraz f musi być większa lub równa 50;Values e and f must be equal or bigger than 50;Values e and f must be equal or bigger than 50;Values e and f must be bigger than 50;Values e and f must be bigger than 50
Trójnik sk.współosiowy;Tee-piece slanted coaxial;Tee-piece slanted coaxial;Tee-piece slanted coaxial;Tee-piece slanted coaxial